It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's a little cuter than the photo.
ちょっと写真より可愛いじゃん
Is it true?
本当ですか?
not at all.
全然
We were making a lot of pictures together.
結構写真作り合ってたんで
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
Have you been talked to quite a lot?
結 構声かけられたりした?
But you were seen, right?
でも見られたりしたっしょ?
What do you think?
どうですかね?
It's cute.
可愛いですね
My hobby is photography.
カメラが趣味でさ
I think you realize it now.
今気づいてると思うけど
Why are you spinning it?
なんで回してるんですか?
My hobby is taking pictures of memories with my camera.
カメラ趣味で思い出を撮ってて
Is it okay to turn it around?
回して回っても平気ですか?
If you don't like it, I'll turn off the camera.
ちょっと嫌だったらカメラ止めるから
Is it okay if I feel like that?
そういう感じだったら平気かな?
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいですけど
If only for a little while.
ちょっとなら
Even his personality is good.
性格までいいんですね
It's very stylish.
めっちゃオシャレだ
There's a core shop.
コア屋さんあるんで
It's called Matsuya.
松屋って言うんですけど
Ah, I know.
あ、 知ってる
I like it.
好きですよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Actually, it was planned to be Mac.
本当はマックの予定だったんだけど
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
It's just a little cute though.
ほんだけちょっと可愛いけど
There's a lot to recommend here.
ここね、結構おすすめのがあってさ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you have any likes or dislikes?
好き嫌いはある?
I don't really like it.
あんまり嫌いですよ
That's right.
そうなんだ
I highly recommend meat and tofu on the next page.
ここね、結構 次のページに 肉豆腐とか 結構おすすめなの
That's right.
そうなんだ
Can I have something to eat?
食べさせてもらっていいですか?
Yeah.
うん
You're so kind.
優しいね
Can I drink alcohol?
お酒飲めるの?
If only for a little while.
ちょっとなら
Can I have a drink?
ちょっと飲める?
Lemon vinegar is highly recommended.
レモン酢は結構おすすめだから
Let's have a toast together.
一緒に乾杯しましょう
Does the time look okay?
時間大丈夫そう?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Shall we have a toast?
乾杯しよっか
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
cheers.
乾杯
It feels good.
いい感じですね
Do you usually drink alcohol?
お酒とか普段飲むの?
I don't drink, so I'm pretty weak.
飲まなくて、結構弱いんで
I don't drink at home.
家飲みとかしないんだ
I don't think so.
しないですね
So, can I just leave it to you that someone special will come over for drinks?
じゃあ特別な人が飲んでくるってことに しといてもらっていい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it okay to like or dislike it?
好き嫌いとか平気かな?
You can eat pretty much anything.
わりと何でも食べれますよ
Do you cook for yourself?
自炊とかするの?
Yeah.
うん
I'll do a lot of work for you.
結構してもらう
What are you going to make?
何作るの?
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
Is it like just adding hot water?
お湯入れて終わりみたいな感じ?
It doesn't happen often, but I do make it quite a bit.
それもたまにはないけど、結構作りますよ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Would you like to pay some money?
ちょっとお金払うか
Make it for me too.
俺にも作ってよ
Well, if we become friends.
まあ、仲良くなったら
Please come and see us.
ぜひぜひ
Next time, if you go to various places,
今度ね、色んな所行ってくれたら、
Walking around town, I felt so happy that I could see them.
街歩いてて、 見られる感じに 嬉しくなっちゃいましたね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だな
I wonder if I'm being watched.
見られてるのかなっていう
On the contrary, I'm sorry.
ちょっと逆に、申し訳ないですよ
I feel like it's me.
僕でねって感じだけど
What kind of scenery did some people have?
どう いう風景の人があった?
It feels like I have some leeway.
それは余裕みたいな感じが
Ho
ほ
Hey, hey.
い ほい
Then I'll be angry.
じゃあ僕怒ります
Are you Menteen?
メ ンティーンですか?
I'm angry today.
今日怒るんですけど
I'm the cutest thing ever.
僕、今まであったら一番可愛いですよ
happy.
嬉しい
Would you like to celebrate your first time and have a toast?
初めて記念ってことにして、 乾杯でもしますか?
nice.
いいね
It's like holding it with both hands.
両手で持つ感じだね
Can I ask you to tell me that you love me?
好きだよとか言ってもらっていい?
He'll do it.
やってくれるんだ
That's impossible.
無理ですね
Seriously.
マジで
I want to eat toast.
トース食べたいな
Feel like a mother.
お母さんみたいな感じを
Plus, you look more sexy.
プ ラス、色気出してきたね
good?
いい?
Wait a minute, okay?
ちょっとじゃあ、いいですか?
I can't open it.
開けない
I can't open this.
これじゃあ、開けない
It's cute.
可愛いですね
Looks like a model photographing a model.
モデル撮るモデルみたいだわ
Sorry.
ごめんね
What do you do when you get so drunk?
こんなに酔わせてどうするの?
We got some really good kids, didn't we?
めちゃくちゃ良い子供もらえたじゃないですか
What do you do when you get drunk?
酔わせてどうするの?
It's getting wet and falling.
すいてきて落ちてる
A little no good.
ちょっとダメ
You look like an older sister.
お姉さんみたいですね
It might be a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいかもしれないです
Really?
本当に?
More embarrassing?
もっと恥ずかしい?
It might be a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいかもしれない
Her smile is cute too.
笑顔も可愛いですね
It's trash, still.
ゴミだね、まだ
Was it on?
ついてた?
It's cute.
かわいいね
I'm still nervous, so I asked him to hang out with me for a few more drinks.
まだ緊張してて、 もう少しお酒とか一緒に付き合ってもらって
good?
いい?
That's fine.
いい ですよ
Well then, thank you for your hard work.
じゃあ、お疲れ
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ
After all, I like kind people.
やっぱり優しい人が好きだから
What kind of kindness is there?
どういう感じの優しさとかあるの?
There are many types of kindness.
優しさにもいろいろ種類あるじゃん
Types of kindness?
優しさの種類?
Are you casual or have a kind personality?
さりげなげとか、 性格的に優しいのか、
Is it behaviorally friendly?
行動的に優しいのか
People who are kind in their behavior might get a little nervous.
行動的に優しい人はちょっと キュンってするかもしれない
Tell me something that made you excited so far.
今までキュンとしたこと教えてよ
Well, I wonder what it is.
えー、何だろう
Quite casually, body touching, etc.
結構、さりげなく ボディータッチとか、
This might make you excited.
これだと、 キュンってするかも
This may be a large group, a large group.
これは大団、大団のかもしれない
It's like, don't come over here.
それは、ちょっとこっち来ないのとか、
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じの?
forever.
ずっと
What was the situation like?
シチュエーション、どんな感じだったの?
Situation?
シチュエーション?
I also want to engage in conversations like this,
俺もこんな会話と付き合いたいからさ、
Let me make a little note.
ちょっとメモらせてもらうんで
But after all, just like this,
でも やっぱりこうやってちょっと、
Have a drink, go to a hotel, etc.
お 酒飲んで、 ホテル行ってとか、
I guess I like that kind of thing after all.
そういうのは、やっぱり好きかなーって
Oh, are you serious?
あ、マジですか?
He's an adult.
大人ですね
I don't know if you're an adult, but you're not drunk at all yet, are you?
大人かわからんけど、 まだ全然酔ってないっしょ?
Yeah.
うん
But it might be getting a little hot.
でもちょっと、 熱くなってきたかもしれない
It might be getting a little hot.
ちょっと熱くなってきたかも
But I came here a little drunk.
でもちょっと酔って、 来ちゃったよ
Well, it's a bit no, no, no.
え、ちょっとダメダメダメ
Because I'll get drunk.
酔っちゃうから
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
Do you want to play games?
ゲームとかします?
What do we do when it comes to doing it with two people?
2人でやるってなると、 何するんだろう?
It's like playing rock, paper, scissors, etc., and the loser ends up drinking more.
ジャンケンとかで、 負けたほうが飲んでいくみたいな
If that's the case, would you mind if I go out with you for a little while?
そんなくらいの感じで、 ちょっと付き合ってもらってもいい?
Then let's play rock, paper, scissors.
じゃあジャンケンで
Are you going?
いきますか
Goo at first.
最初はグー
Rock, paper, scissors.
ジャンケン
What?
え、なに?
It's goo.
グーです
Is it goo?
グーなの?
a,
あ、
I lost!
負 けちゃった!
Well then, would you mind a moment?
じゃあ ちょっといいすか?
Yay!
や ったー
What does it taste like?
どんな味するの?
It's delicious.
美味しいよ
It's not sweet.
甘くない
You haven't been drinking, have you?
飲んでないでしょ?
I want to feel it.
感触したくて
Because I looked at the camera.
カメラしみたからさ
Where are you drinking?
飲んでるとこ?
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいな
Except for Osage.
オセジとか抜きに
I might have gotten a little drunk.
ちょっと酔ってきちゃったかもしれないな
Again!
またまたー!
Shall we have a drink or something?
飲み合い1個とかしちゃう?
You can't drink this, right?
こっち飲めないでしょ?
Can I drink it?
飲める?
Shall we have a drink?
飲んでみようかな
Delicious, delicious.
美味しい美味しい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Well, actually, you can change the seasoning.
ちょっとね、実はね、味付け変えれるんですよ、
this.
これ
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
Lemon sour.
レモンサワー
Wait a minute, I'm making it now.
ちょっと待ってね、今作ってるから
Do you make it?
作るの?
Soft lips.
唇柔らかい
Try making a kissy face or something.
ちょっとキス顔とかしてみてよ
Kiss face?
キス顔?
Are you going to make a kissy face?
キス顔するか
Oh, did you do it?
あ、しちゃった?
Just a little bit, just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけしちゃった?
It's a bit like that, it's a punishment game.
ちょっとあれだね、罰ゲームなんで
Can you kiss me one more time?
もう一回ちょっと、俺とキスしてもらっていいですか?
It's so naughty.
めっちゃエッチだね
It hasn't come at all.
全然来てないじゃん
Not at all, I'm pretty drunk.
全然、結構酔ってきてるよ
It really hasn't changed.
ほんま変わらないんだね
I think it's a little red.
ちょっと赤くなってると思う
I really don't know.
ほんまにわかんない
My skin is naturally white.
肌は、確かにもともと白いから
Hey, it's white.
ね、白いよね
My hair is combed somehow.
なんか毛がとかしてるの
That's how much sunscreen I wear.
そんなに日焼け止め塗るぐらいだよ
Can I paint it too? Me too.
塗っていいすか、俺も
picture?
え?
Are you going to paint it?
塗っちゃうの?
Ah, your cheeks are so soft.
あ、ほっぱい柔らかいね
It's so big.
す ーごいちくびいっぱいなんだね
Tiny?
ちくび?
It's not small.
ちくびじゃないよ
It's a little off.
ちょっと引いてるじゃん
I haven't pulled it.
引いてないよ
I absentmindedly pulled it out.
ぼーっと引いてきた
Well then, I feel like it's okay.
じゃあちょっと、えいって感じ
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいな
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
So this is my kissing face or something.
じゃあこっちは、自分のキス顔とかさ
Take a look.
見て みて
Kiss face?
キス顔?
own face.
自分の顔
Isn't it a little red?
なんかちょっと赤くない?
Well then, it's just me, with a silly face.
じゃあちょっと自分のさ、 ヘラ顔さ
A crazy face?
ヘラ顔?
It'll be there in a little while.
ちょっとちいたらあるからさ
Try licking it.
舐めてみて
Because I have these.
これちいたらだから
What will you do?
どんなにする?
It's a little salty.
ちょっとしょっぱいよ
Try licking it.
ぺろぺろしてみて
It's a little salty.
ちょっとしょっぱいよね
Just this.
ちょっと これで
way way way way
ウェイウェイウェイウェイ
From the moment I entered the hotel,
さ っきから、ホテル入ったときから、
I won't touch it.
触らないですよ
Oh, it's getting bigger.
え、大きくなってる
It's gotten a little bigger.
ちょっと大きくなっちゃった
Don't touch it at all.
絶対触っちゃダメだよ
What is that?
なにそれ?
You should never touch this.
絶対触っちゃダメだよこれ
Is it okay to touch it?
触っちゃダメなの?
Yeah, a little bit.
うん、ちょっと
Absolutely not, absolutely.
絶対ダメだよ、絶対
Absolutely no?
絶対ダメ?
Oh, wait.
あ、ちょっと
It's a bit of a bummer, isn't it?
ちょっと、気持ちいんぽって感じだね
picture?
え?
What is that?
なにそれ?
I'm just kidding a bit.
ちょっとふざけちゃってるから
I drank it.
飲んじゃった
Your lips are really red.
めちゃくちゃ唇の赤いね
Should I keep it cold?
冷やしておく?
Yeah.
うん
Let it cool down a bit?
ちょっと冷やしておく?
Yeah.
うん
It's really spacious.
めっちゃ広いね
You'll get used to it, right?
慣れるでしょ?
yes?
そう?
Isn't it a screw?
ビスじゃんか
Yay.
イエーイ
It's getting a little expensive.
ちょっと高くなってきたね
I might have come a little closer.
ちょっと寄ってきちゃったかも
Their faces are completely different sizes.
顔の大きさ全然違うね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I just don't recognize it.
ちょっと認識してないよ
The camera.
カメラが
Can I stop by?
お立ち寄りしてもいい?
Yeah.
うん
I can kiss you forever.
ずっとキスできるね
Where do you say it's raw liver?
どこが生肝体だって言ってるの?
picture?
え?
Raw liver body?
生肝体?
What will you put in it?
何入れてくれるんだって
Would you like to have a little text?
ちょっとテックスしとく?
picture?
え?
What is that?
なにそれ?
Like, together.
一緒にさ、みたいな
a!
あ!
You can enter it yourself!
自分から入れてくれるんだ!
Can I put it in?
入れるの?
Let's start with Ive.
ちょっとアイブから始めようか
What about this?
どうこれ?
You've been standing for a while.
ちょっと立ってきたね
Did you stand up?
立ってきた?
It's temporary.
仮細だね
Aren't you going to come out for a while?
ちょっと 出ちゃうんじゃない?
Stop it for a second.
ちょっとやめてよ
I'm out.
出ちゃいました
Shall we have a little tex?
ちょっとテックスしちゃう?
Ah, it's warm.
あ、温かいじゃん
Is it warm?
温 かい?
I came over.
寄ってきちゃった
Really?
本当に?
I'll check if it's coming along properly.
ちゃんと寄ってるから確認するよ
picture?
え?
Here.
ここで
Your feet are so beautiful.
めっちゃ足綺麗だね
White skin.
肌白
Are you taking care of yourself?
なんかケアしてるの?
No, not at all.
いや、全然してなくて
Is this what you didn't do?
してないでこれなの?
I haven't.
してないよ
Thank you very much.
やに感謝だね
Don't you hate having your feet touched?
足とか触られるの嫌いじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
New material?
新素材?
It's so smooth.
すげーすべすべじゃん
Seriously?
まじ?
Don't touch it with your feet.
ちょっと足で触っちゃダメだよ
Just don't touch it with your feet.
ちょっと 足で触っちゃダメだよ
Please touch it in reverse.
逆に触ってください
It's like, ``Please.''
お願いします って感じになってます
Have you ever touched it with your feet?
足で触ったりしたことある?
Touch it with your feet?
足で触る?
like this?
こう?
No.
ダメ
please.
お願い
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's super cute.
超かわいいじゃん
I can see your pants.
パ ンツ見えてるし
It had both legs.
両足だった
I'm a little drunk too.
ちょっと俺も酔ってるからさ
Shall we come out?
出ちゃう?
No.
ダメ
Because he touched me with his feet.
足で触ってくれたからさ
Check out the articles on pants.
パンツの記事刊チェック
Check article publication?
記事刊チェック?
Please publish an article.
ちょっと 記事刊ね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
We shot for about 5 hours.
5時間くらい撮って
No way.
そんなダメ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'll stop in 15 seconds.
15秒でやめるからさ
Wow, that's really egotistical.
うわーめちゃくちゃエゴいじゃん
Please publish an article.
ちょっと記事刊ね
a little bit.
ちょっと
No.
ダメ
It's no good.
ダメだって
picture?
え?
I don't hate it at all.
全然嫌がってないじゃん
It's no good.
ダメだって
please.
お願い
It hasn't been 10 seconds yet.
まだ10秒経ってないよ
ちょっとまだ10秒経ってない
15 seconds passed
15秒経
There is no such thing.
って ない
It doesn't hurt though.
痛くないけど
Will my clothes get dirty?
洋服汚れちゃうか
No.
ダメ
See?
ほらね
Then I should take my clothes off too, right?
じゃあ 俺も脱げばいいでしょ?
Hoi hoi hoi hoi.
ほいほいほいほい
Because it's a game.
ゲームだから
ゲ ームだから
game game game.
ゲームゲームゲーム
Because that's the kind of game it is.
そういうゲームだから
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
No.
ダメ
Yes, yes.
はいはい
If you feel that way, it's game over.
あんなに感じたらゲームオーバーだよ
Yeah.
うん
pa
パ
Can I have a look?
ンツ 見せてもらってもいい?
I'm a little embarrassed though.
ちょっと恥ずかしいんだけど
I want to take pictures of her being shy.
恥ずかしがってるところが撮りたいな
What color is it today?
今日は何色ですって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What color do you paint?
どういう色描くの?
Are there many colors like this?
こういう色が多いの?
Did you compete today?
今日もしかして勝負したっけ?
What do you think?
どうだろう
Are you going to waste it on me?
こっち無駄あげれたりするの?
Don't do it because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいからダメ
Please sit down for a moment.
ちょっと座ってもらってさ
Isn't it okay if I take my clothes off?
俺脱がすんだったらいいっしょ?
Are you going to take it off?
脱がしちゃうの?
Let's take off our clothes and play together.
脱がし合い子しようよ
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいよ
Will it break first?
先に折れる?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I can't show it to you yet.
ちょっとまだ見せれないな
Hair treatment is sweet.
毛の処理甘くて
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's Oshaman.
おしゃまなんだ
That feeling is really nice.
その感じめっちゃいいね
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
It feels really good.
めっちゃいいじゃんこの感じ
Don't read a lot.
結構読むな
Isn't it enough?
足りないんじゃないの?
Is it okay if I do something embarrassing?
恥ずかしいことしちゃっていいですか?
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいよ
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
恥ずかしい
Even the armpits are beautiful.
脇まで綺麗なんだね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいんだ
No way, I'll take that much.
ダメそんなに取っちゃう
It's extremely spacious.
めちゃくちゃ広いね
It's me.
自分がさ
Have you ever seen yourself being squeezed?
もまれてるところ自分で見たことある?
do not have.
ない
Look, look.
見て見て
It's cute.
かわいいね
But it feels good.
でも 気持ちいいんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No.
ダメ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No.
ダメ
Show me just a little bit of your face.
ちょっと顔びらだけ見せて
Come snuggle with me.
寄り添ってみて
It's easy to stand.
立ちやすいんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No.
ダ メ
Can I kiss you and turn you around?
キスして回していいの?
It's really hot.
めっちゃイッチだ
It's a little hot.
ちょっと熱いっしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいよ
I'll take my clothes off too.
俺も脱ぐからさ
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い痛い
It's a string.
ひもかんじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's string bread.
ひもパンだろ
It's pretty cool.
結構イッチですね
I caught a Hiyahimo Pan.
ひやひもパン釣ったんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Samshima.
さましま
Sorry.
ごめんね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Look here.
こっち見て
No.
ダメ
Shall we take our clothes off together?
一緒に脱ぐのか
Se-no.
せ ーの
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいよ
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's ingrained.
しみついてんじゃん
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
what happened?
どうしたの?
But.
でもさ
No more.
もうダメ
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
No, it's embarrassing.
ダメ恥ずかしい
Just a little bit.
ちょっと ちょっと
pa
パ
I: It's bread.
イ パンなんだ
It looks like a child's pussy.
子供マンコみたい
Can I ask you something more embarrassing?
もっと恥ずかしいことお願いしていい?
Hold me from below.
下から抱えてさ
Please spread it out and show me.
広げて見せてみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
like this?
こう?
Show me like that.
そうやって見せて
I'll give you money.
お金あげちゃうよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Look here.
こっち見て
I got 10,000.
1万入りました
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Spread your legs over here.
足こっち広げて